{
    "id": "aaa00dacae8642afad069da24e836e3c",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I understand that he …………………… .. absent yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76c5a04325204abfa4d92f55bbc4ae4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wood always …………………… .. on water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "float",
                "floats",
                "will float"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "362498503ff946a48e06937f56b831ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………… heavily for a week and the rivers are overflowing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rained",
                "is raining",
                "has been raining"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "20d01a9eeda74a21a3c1d2973e15e122"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are some birds that …………………… . every year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "migrate",
                "migrates",
                "migrating"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4720f5aee3b4272832d6410b2c24a25"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. to Singapore once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have gone",
                "have been",
                "had gone",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "215dd8f579404092bd9655b30e72e910"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… .. dinner an hour ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "186990b0cfa74a7da1ca912bdbead906"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… .. nothing to eat since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3833c4060ea244fd8e709d5fa3417d30"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her health has improved since she ……………………… to her native village.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "had returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c34f2095e944ce59cf4420a36b15f6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will catch the first bus that …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "is coming",
                "comes"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2514dbbdc2d6469cae0df0b28a765991"
        },
        {
            "question": "See that the patient …………………… . complete rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "gets",
                "got"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f464c8f4d3f3418083bea7c263e2e57d"
        }
    ]
}